嘿 我前两天看了个电影预告片
Hey, so I saw a movie trailer the other day.
蝙蝠侠怎么可能跟超人大战呢?
How could Batman possibly fight Superman?
我是说 这也太傻了吧?
I mean, isn't that dumb?
或许他用了氪星石
Maybe he uses Kryptonite.
蝙蝠侠多金啊
Well, Batman's got a lot of money.
或许他造了一件媲美超人一切能力的战衣
Maybe he builds a suit that can do everything Superman can do.
不 不 此言差矣
No, no, no, no, no.
我看过那部电影 叫钢铁侠
I've seen that movie. It's called Iron Man.
什么情况?
What is happening?
母鸡啊
I don't know.
太和谐了
But it's beautiful.
现在本·阿弗莱克都能演蝙蝠侠了?
And now Ben Affleck is Batman?
他在莎翁情史中表现很棒
Oh, he was great in Shakespeare in Love.
哦 那我们下次闺蜜之夜看这部电影
Ooh, we should watch that next girls' night.
我们可以来个双片放映
We could do a double feature
加上莱昂纳多·迪卡普里奥版的罗密欧和朱丽叶
with the Leonardo DiCaprio Romeo + Juliet.
好 我想看莱昂
Oh, I love me some Leo.
转瞬即逝啊
And it's gone.
大家好
Oh, hello, everyone.
我非常开心地宣布我感觉好多了
I am happy to report I'm feeling much better.
恭喜你啊
Good for you.
我发烧退了 我的鼻子不堵了
My fever is gone, my sinuses are pressure-free,
我的痰也像优胜美地瀑布一样清澈了
and my mucus is as clear as a Yosemite waterfall.
喜闻乐见啊
Glad to hear it.
我明天就可以回去工作了
I'll be able to return to work tomorrow.
耶
Yay.
你们怎么都不开心呢?
Well, why isn't everyone happy?
你们的小小阳光可以再次闪耀了
Your little ray of sunshine is ready to beam again.
- 你真不知道原因?  - 不知道
- You really don't know why?  - No.
但我知道他的"耶"是反话
But I knew that his “yay” was sarcastic.
我这洞察力对一个拉肚子拉的跟下雨一样的
Not bad for a guy whose last bowel movement
人来说已经不错了
sounded like rain on a roof.
让我帮你回顾一下
Let me refresh your memory.
Penny啊
Penny,
帮我在胸上抹药膏
rub Vicks on my chest.
Sheldon 我帮你做了早饭
Sheldon, I cooked you breakfast.
我给你铺了床
I made your bed.
我查了你的嘴巴看有没有长疮
I checked your mouth for thrush.
你可以自己抹胸口的
You can rub your own chest.
好吧 对星球上所有的男性毛手毛脚
Oh, sure, grope every other male on the planet,
但偏偏对我划清界限
but draw the line with me.
我从公司给你带了爱的包裹
I brought you a little care package from work.
这是我们最新制作的抗病毒药
It's our latest antiviral
和最棒的鼻塞药
and the best decongestant we make.
我希望笑是最好的良药
I hope laughter is the best medicine,
因为爱的包裹根本就是笑话
'cause this care package is a joke.
嘿 她不辞辛苦...
Hey, she came all the way here...
你最好跟食物一起服用
You're gonna want to take these with food.
Sheldon 别像个孩子似的
Sheldon, stop being a baby
让Emily给你瞧瞧
and let Emily take a look at you.
她是个皮肤科医生
She's a dermatologist.
我读过医学系
I went to medical school.
这样的话 拜托你
Well, in that case, try removing
把站在你旁边的那坨
the irritating patch of brown skin
烦人的棕色皮肤移除掉
standing next to you.
好了 给你
All right, here you go.
Leonard 我要死了
Leonard, I'm dying.
你不会死 只是流感而已
You're not dying. It's just the flu.
我想吃鸡汤面
I asked for chicken noodle.
但我却看到了鸡肉星星汤 折磨死我了
This is chicken and stars. It's killing me.
那根本就不是鸡汤面 我说错了吗?
I never did get that chicken noodle, did I?
# 宇宙一度又烫又稠密 #
# Our whole universe was in a hot, dense state #
# 140亿年前终于爆了炸... 等着瞧! #
# Then nearly 14 billion years ago expansion started... Wait! #
# 地球开始降温 #
# The Earth began to cool #
# 自养生物来起哄 穴居人发明工具 #
# The autotrophs began to drool, Neanderthals developed tools #
# 我们建长城 我们建金字塔 #
# We built the Wall # # We built the pyramids #
# 数学 自然科学 历史 揭开神秘 #
# Math, Science, History, unraveling the mystery #
# 一切由大爆炸开始 #
# That all started with a big bang #
生活大爆炸 第九季第13集
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hdscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 打酱油的影纸   校对: UUUU吃吃吃吃
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hdscg.com/==--
翻译: 波特妹子 肉肉君 小黄不小黄 猫呗 無限月讀 AU薇
嗨 Sheldon
Hi, Sheldon.
嗨
Hello.
你感觉好些了吗?
Are you feeling any better?
肉体上 是的 但我因为大家
Physically, yes, but I'm upset
没理由地生我气感到失落
because everyone's mad at me for no good reason.
你可以试试用一种温柔贴心的方法
Why don't you tell me what happened,
告诉我发生的一切
and in a gentle, loving way,
我会给你解释你哪里做的不对
I'll explain to you why you're wrong.
你知道吗 当你生病时
You know how, when you're sick,
你可以耍脾气并说出你想要的一切
you're allowed to be cranky and say whatever you want
而不需要顾及别人的感觉?
and other people's feelings don't matter?
哦 要温柔贴心 这看来会很难了
Ooh. Gentle and loving. This is gonna be tricky.
我高烧38度
I had a 101 fever.
如果这我都不能指使我朋友 那该是什么时候?
If that's not a time to verbally abuse my loved ones, when is?
Sheldon 当你生病时 你是有点令人... 无法忍受
Sheldon, when you're sick, you can be... unbearable.
这就是为什么你的朋友们
That's why your friends have been known
加班或者偷偷去看电影
to work late or sneak out to the movies
或者在神经学研讨会结束三天后
or stay at a neurobiology conference
还待在那里
three days after it's ended.
你在密歇根州待了一个星期就为了不在我身边?
You stayed in Michigan all week to avoid being around me?
不 不 不光是这个
No, no, not just that.
我是说...
I mean...
底特律下雨夹雪时特别漂亮
Detroit is beautiful when it's sleeting.
知道吗 我不是唯一一个
You know, I'm not the only one
在生病时感觉不开心的人
who's unpleasant when they're sick.
当Penny食物中毒时 她呕吐声音特别大
When Penny got food poisoning, she threw up so loudly
我都听不见电视声
I could barely hear the television.
哦 外面有点动静
Ooh, I just heard something.
可能是冰雹 可能是枪声
Might be hail, might be gunfire.
不管是啥我都要去拍照 拜拜
Either way, I'm gonna go take pictures. Bye.
嘿 Stuart
Hey, Stuart.
嘿 Sheldon呢?
Hey. Where's Sheldon?
- 还生病吗?  - 没 他很好
- Still sick?   - No, he's fine.
我们只是需要休息一会
We just needed a little break.
嗯 我知道了
Yeah, I get that.
当我把他的漫画给他时
When I brought him his comics the other day,
他说"太好了 死神真的上门了"
he said, "Oh, great, Death is literally at my door."
他对每个人都那么混蛋
He was being a jerk to everyone.
别往心里去
Don't take it personally.
哦 我吃了这么多抗抑郁药
Oh, I'm on so many antidepressants,
就算我想的话也不可能
I couldn't if I wanted to.
我希望我们能不带Sheldon做更多事
I wish we could do more stuff without Sheldon.
我一直都这么想
I wish that all the time.
一般是我吹灭生日蜡烛时候许的愿
Usually before I blow out birthday candles.
Amy也隔离了他一些时间
You know, Amy took some time off from him.
真的巩固了他们的感情
Really improved their relationship.
嗯 不错
Huh. Okay.
只要结局不是我们和他性交
As long as it doesn't end with us having coitus with him,
我都参加
I'm in.
我们应该去旅游或者干些别的
We should all take a trip or something.
知道吗 Penny和我一直在讨论
You know, Penny and I have been talking
在拉斯维加斯过周末
about taking a weekend in Vegas.
我们应该都去
Maybe we should all go.
Bernie会喜欢的
Bernie would love that.
哦! 哦! 我们还可以坐
Oh! Ooh! Maybe we could get
那些派对巴士去那里
one of those party buses to take us there.
听起来很有趣
That sounds really fun.
嗯 听起来不错
Yeah, that sounds fun.
一个派对永不停的派对巴士
A party-bus party don't stop.
哦! 我说"派对" 你说"巴士"
Ooh! When I say "party," you say "bus."
- 不  - 不
- No.  - No
- 不  - 不!
- No.  - No!
所以 我和大家在讨论
So, the guys and I were talking about
租一辆派对巴士然后所有人去拉斯维加斯
renting a party bus and everyone going to Vegas.
哦 这不错啊
Oh, that could be fun.
说清楚点 你说的派对巴士里面有
But just to be clear, you mean a party bus
酒和饮料
with booze and music, right,
而不是果汁盒还有电子游戏吧
not, like, juice boxes and video games?
对
Yes.
Howard的生日派对你把我送去就可以了
And Howard's birthday was a drop-off party.
你不需要留下来
You didn't have to stay.
好啊 加我一个
Well, I'm in.
- 我们什么时候去?  - 这个周末
- When are we going?  - This weekend.
哦 我们要去哪里啊?
Oh, where are we going?
去拉斯维加斯 但是...
Well, Vegas, but...
呃 像大西洋城一样还没有糖吃?
Ugh, Atlantic City without the taffy?
算了吧
No, thank you.
没关系 其实我们没打算请你一起去
That's fine, 'cause actually you're not invited.
这... 这太伤人了
Well, now... well, that's hurtful.
Sheldon 你都不喜欢那地方
Oh, Sheldon, you don't even like it there.
虽然我觉得那地方
I can consider a place
就是美国的便池
America's urinal cake
但是偶尔去去还是不错的啊
and still enjoy the occasional visit.
这次不行
Not this time.
好吧 我就和Wolowitz一起玩吧
Oh, fine. Then I'll just hang out with Wolowitz.
- 他也去  - 那我就和Raj...
- He's coming, too.  - Well, then Raj and I will...
- 他也不行  - 好吧 那我和Stuart玩
- Nope.  - Very well. Stuart.
好啊 就他吧
Oh, great. Do that.
呃 Stuart
Ugh. Stuart.
Sheldon 有什么新鲜事吗?
Hi, Sheldon. What's new?
我们的朋友都是混蛋 宝宝很生气
Our friends are jerks, and I'm mad at all of them.
我问的是"新鲜"事 不过算了吧
I said, “What's new?” but sure.
你能相信他们打算
Can you believe they planned a trip
抛下我去拉斯维加斯吗?
to Las Vegas and didn't invite me?
你是不是没有道歉
Did you refuse to apologize
还搞得好像他们生气是他们傻?
and act like they were stupid for being mad?
我还是喜欢以前
You know, I liked it better when there was still
我们之间还有秘密的时候
a little mystery left in our relationship.
所有人都在想办法照顾你
Everyone tried to take care of you,
但是你还是对他们那么刻薄
and you were nothing but mean to them.
你竟然不站在我这边
I can't believe you're not on my side.
你车子里的收音机被偷走的时候我可是站在你这边的
I was on your side when someone stole your car radio.
那个时候你不支持我支持谁啊?
Who else's side could you have been on?
我不知道
I don't know.
一个热爱音乐的痴心浪子?
A music-loving hobo with a heart of gold?
Sheldon 我知道你很不高兴
Sheldon, I understand that you're upset
因为你感觉被排除在外了
because you feel left out,
但是我真不知道我们说那么多干嘛
but I don't know why we're even talking about this.
你去和他们道歉啊
Just apologize to them.
好吧 看来我要这样才能和他们一起出去玩了
Fine, if that's what it takes to go on their dumb trip.
你能不能真心实意地去道个歉啊
Maybe you could try apologizing because you actually feel bad.
这叫同情心
It's called empathy.
你应该好好学学
It's something you could work on.
我有同情心啊
I have empathy.
看着
Watch.
Leonard给我烧了汤 我还对他那么刻薄
Leonard made me soup, and I was mean to him.
太好了
Great.
再说一遍 这次不要搞得好像你第一次当人
Now try it as if this isn't your first day as a person.
好吧
Fine.
Leonard给我烧了汤 我还对他那么刻薄
Leonard made me soup, and I was mean to him.
嘿 我有点感觉了
Hey, I felt a little something.
让我再试试
Let me try again.
Leonard给我烧了汤 我还对他那么刻薄
Leonard made me soup, and I was mean to him.
我的确对他很刻薄
I was mean to him.
他肯定很难过
He must have felt terrible.
现在我也很难过了
Oh, now I feel terrible.
真棒!
Neat!
很高兴能帮上忙
Glad I could help.
现在轮到你了 让我看看你
Now let me see you feel bad for lying
对我撒谎躲在底特律的事自责的样子
and staying in Detroit longer than you needed to.
我真的好难过
I feel so, so bad.
嘿 我们真厉害
Hey, we're both great at this.
Leonard 准备好 我要道歉了
Leonard, get ready for an apology.
就好像奈特·沙马兰的电影结尾一样
And with the added twist of an M. Night Shyamalan movie,
这次我是真心的
I'm going to mean it.
啊 就像其他我看过的
Ah, so like every other
奈特·沙马兰电影结尾一样
M. Night Shyamalan movie I've seen,
你又剧透了
you spoil it in advance.
嘿 你不知道布鲁斯威利斯是个死人
Hey, if you didn't know Bruce Willis
可不是我的错
was dead the whole time, that's not on me.
好吧
Okay.
开始啦
Here it comes.
在我生病的时候
You tried to take care of me
你努力照顾我 而我却对你那么刻薄
when I was sick, and I was mean to you.
这种态度没有借口
There's no excuse for that.
而且我非常的抱歉
And I'm truly sorry.
谢谢
Thank you.
我很感激
I appreciate that.
我希望你知道这歉意是很真诚的
I want you to know that that is sincere.
我确实... 很后悔
I-I do feel bad.
我不是为了可以和你们一起去旅游才这么说的
I'm not just saying it to be included on your trip.
同样也很感激
Appreciate that, too.
太棒了
Terrific.
现在只剩下你邀请我一起去了
Now all that's left is for you to invite me to come.
然后我问 "你确定吗?"
Me to ask, "Are you sure?"
你说 "当然"
You to say, "Absolutely."
然后我无奈地总结说
And then me to bring it home with,
"对你这张小脸我怎么能拒绝呢?"
"How could I say no to that face?"
你还是不能去
You're still not coming.
什么? 但是我真心诚意地道歉了啊
What? But I apologized and I meant it.
我知道我们很少玩这个游戏
I know that we don't play this game very often,
但是你玩错了
but you're doing it wrong.
Sheldon 我接受你的歉意 但是你生病的时候
Sheldon, I accept your apology, but you upset
惹得很多人都生气了
a lot of people while you were sick.
我没有权利说你可以来就能来啊
I'm not in a position to just say you can come.
好吧
Well, all right.
假如我和他们都道歉了呢?
What if I apologize to all of them?
好吧 假如你和所有人都道歉了
Fine, if you apologize to everyone,
他们说没问题了 那你就可以来了
they all say it's okay, then yes, you can come.
接受挑战!
Challenge accepted!
听起来就像Sheldon Cooper的道歉之旅
Sounds like it's time for the Sheldon Cooper Apology Tour.
我希望这次
Well, I hope it's as much fun
和Sheldon Cooper菜单拼写检查记一样好玩
as the Sheldon Cooper Spell-Checks Local Menus Tour.
天啊!
My goodness!
你还记得 "附送庐笋"吗?
Do you remember “comes with apsparagus”?
Howard和Bernadette
Howard and Bernadette,
你们在我生病的时候努力安抚我
you tried to comfort me when I was ill,
而我对你们的态度却很糟糕
and I treated you terribly.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我很感动
I'm impressed.
不不不 等等
No, no, no, wait.
我还没完
I'm not done.
请允许我用一场感天动地的表演
Allow me to underscore my sentiment
来强调一下我的歉意
with a haunting rendition
一首用排箫吹奏的
of Brenda Lee's "I'm Sorry"
布伦达·李的 "对不起"
played on the pan flute.
- 你的歉意我们接受了!  - 原谅你了 原谅了!
- Apology accepted!  - Forgiven, forgiven!
好吧 又浪费了八个小时的练习时间
All right, that's eight hours of practice down the drain.
为了纪念这场道歉
And to memorialize this occasion,
这是你们的纪念T恤
here are your commemorative T-shirts.
"Sheldon Cooper向我道歉了"
"Sheldon Cooper apologized to me"
"他让大家和好如初"
"And he made it all better."
你付出了一切的
All you did was offer
细致关怀和悉心照顾
maternal care and affection,
而你收获的却是
and all you received in return
我粗鲁且无知的行为
was rude and insensitive behavior.
你能等等说吗?
Can this wait?
恐怕不行
I'm afraid it can't.
明天就出去旅游了
The trip is tomorrow.
我还有好多歉没道呢
And I have more apologies to make.
好吧 我接受了你的道歉 你给我出去!
Okay, fine, I accept your apology, now get out!
太棒了 你介意拿着这件T恤
Wonderful. would you mind holding up this shirt
- 给我拍张... ?  - Leonard!
- while I take a quick...?  - Leonard!
你在我难受的时候给我带来了漫画书
You brought me my comic books when I wasn't feeling well.
你真是考虑很周到
That-that was thoughtful.
而我却没有体会到你的周全
And I was insensitive.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
谢谢 Sheldon
Thank you, Sheldon.
我很感激
I appreciate that.
我是真心诚意地道歉的 你知道吗?
And I want you to know that I mean it, you know?
这不只是因为我想去拉斯维加斯玩
This isn't me just wanting to go on the trip to Las Vegas.
去拉斯维加斯玩?
What trip to Las Vegas?
这周末每个人
The one everyone's taking
都坐派对巴士去玩
this weekend on the party bus.
当然了 没邀请我
Of course, I wasn't invited.
我可以理解
That would be my understanding.
说个不那么难受的事情
On a less painful subject,
你穿什么码子的T恤?
what size T-shirt do you take?
Raj 你一直都在当个好朋友
Raj, you were being a good friend,
生病不是我讨人嫌的理由
and my illness was no excuse for my behavior.
我希望你能接受我的歉意
I hope that you can accept my apology.
我不会在意的
Of course I do.
Emily 很抱歉我说皮肤科医生
And, Emily, I'm sorry for saying dermatologists
不是真正的医生
aren't real doctors.
我相信你听过很多次都烦了
And I'm sure you're tired of hearing that.
你真的觉得我经常听人这么讲吗?
Do you honestly think I hear that a lot?
你的工作就是挤挤青春痘
Well, I would imagine when your job is popping zits
往老妈妈的脸上打打肉毒杆菌...
and squirting Botox into old lady faces...
够了!
Okay!
够了 要说的是
Okay, the point is
我们接受你的歉意
that we accept your apology.
也许你接受歉意了
Uh, maybe you do.
可他又挖苦我了
He just insulted me again.
他不是故意的
Yeah, but he doesn't mean it.
你为什么护着他?
Why are you defending him?
我想我知道原因
I believe I can answer that.
和我一样
Uh, like me,
Raj是在表达同情心
Raj is demonstrating empathy.
何不接受我的歉意
Now, why don't you accept my apology,
并收下你的免费T恤...
receive your free T-shirt, uh...
我希望最小号就行了
I hope extra small is okay.
不知为何 Wolowitz拿了中号
For some reason Wolowitz took a medium.
我不接受你的歉意
Well, I don't accept your apology.
你要干什么?
What are you doing?
这叫做为自己说话
It's called standing up for myself.
有时候你也该试试
You should try it some time.
那不如这样吧?
Fine, how about this?
这无聊的争吵
You're making me uncomfortable by prolonging
让我觉得不舒服 我希望你别这样
this ridiculous fight, and I wish you'd stop.
你要我别这样?
Oh, you want me to stop?
没问题
No problem.
行了 别走啊!
No, come on, please don't leave!
确认一下 你还去玩吗?
Point of clarification-- are you still going on the trip?
因为如果不去的话...
Because if not...
别担心 你没事的
Don't worry, you're good.
我导致你们吵架 我很抱歉
I caused that fight, I feel terrible.
等等 我可以再真诚一点...
Wait, I can do that better...
我导致你们吵架
I caused that fight.
我很抱歉
I feel terrible.
哇 我也不知道哪个更好
Yeah, wow, I don't know which one I like more.
他俩吵得厉害吗?
So, was the fight really bad?
没有
No.
按吵架来说 吵得可精彩了
As a fight, it was excellent.
她说了难听的话 还摔了门
She used harsh language and slammed the door.
虽然我这么说
Although as I say this,
可也许不是你问的那个意思
that might not have been what you were asking.
你觉得他们还会去吗?
You think they'll still go on the trip?
我知道是吵架过后 我去安慰Emily...
All I know is after the fight I went to Emily's to smooth...
- 他们不会去玩了  - 不会去了
- They're not going on the trip.  - No.
你到底什么毛病?
What is wrong with you?
看看他 关心我的毛病
Look at him, caring about what's wrong with me.
这是顶级的换位思考
That is some top-shelf empathy.
我们该组建个学习小组
Hey, well, we should start a club.
你去向Emily道歉
You went to Emily's to apologize.
而你走后 她在哭
And when you left, she was crying.
是啊
That is true.
我想我该再道歉一次
Well, I suppose I should apologize again.
她还好吗?
Is she okay?
还好 我安慰她了
Yeah, I calmed her down.
可如果Sheldon去拉斯维加斯的话她就不去了
But she's not going to Vegas if he's going.
等等 还有得选择?
Wait, that's an option?
我还以为没得选
I didn't know that was an option.
没事的 因为我已经决定
Well, that is fine, because I've decided
不和你们一块儿去了
that I won't be joining you.
我意识到表达我内疚心情的
I've realized that the most genuine way
最好方法就是让你们
to demonstrate the remorse I feel is to let you
这周末好好玩
have this weekend to yourselves.
你真是太成熟了
That's very mature of you.
我最近也小小地旅行了一回
Well, I've been on a little trip myself recently.
并不是去罪恶之城而是去真诚之城
Not to Sin City but to Sincere City.
带回来的不是尖锐湿疣
Where instead of genital warts, the only growth
而是心智的成长
you'll come back with is personal growth.
下一件T上面写这个吧
And there's your next T-shirt.
喔 瞧瞧这钢管
Ooh, check out the stripper pole.
你知道这意味着什么吗
You know what that means.
Raj在我们上高速之前就会缠在上面吗?
That Raj'll be on it before we make it to the freeway?
真是太了解我了!
You know it!
真是太酷了
This is so cool.
喝点香槟吧!
Let's have champagne!
嗯嗯
Mm-hmm.
我要敬大家一杯
Well, I would like to propose a toast
庆祝这个属于我们的周末...
to a well-deserved weekend of...
你在做甚啊?!
What are you doing?!
我的计划是上国道再跳出来
My plan was to jump out at the state line,
但是我的一个鼻塞掉进马桶里了
but one of my nose plugs fell into the toilet.
你连一个周末都不愿意让我们好过吗?
You couldn't give us just one weekend?
我跟他说了这主意不好
I told him this was a bad idea.
我们怎么办 把他俩踢下去
What do we do-- kick them off?
如果我们在消防局把他俩丢下
If we drop them off at a fire station,
他们就得收留他俩 不能有任何异议
they have to take them; no questions asked.
在这之前 请允许我再跟
Before you do, please give me one more chance
Emily道歉一次
to apologize to Emily.
哦 天啊
Oh, God.
Emily 我很清楚你知道
Emily, as I'm sure you know,
我一直被当做一个怪咖
I'm considered an odd fellow.
但是你不知道的是 尽管我嘴上
But what you don't know is that, while I often
常常说错话 但是我内心深处是善良的
say the wrong thing, in my heart I mean well.
我觉得你是一个
I think that you are
聪明又有魅力的女性
a smart and wonderful woman, you know?
我们都觉得Koothrappali是高攀了你
And we all think that you can do better than Koothrappali.
你懂得 Sheldon...
You know, Sheldon...
嘘 让他说完
Shh, let him finish.
所以 我要为我过去对你造成的冒犯
So, for all the times I've offended you
和未来可能会对你造成的冒犯
and all the times that I'll offend you in the future,
表示歉意
I'm sorry.
谢谢你
Thank you.
好的
Good.
我该走了
Then I'll be leaving now.
没事的 Sheldon
Oh, it's okay, Sheldon.
和我们一块儿去吧
Come with us.
哦 你真是太好了
Oh, that's very kind of you.
但是我觉得我不在你们都会玩得更开心
But I'm sure you'll all have a better time without me.
走吧 stuart
Let's go, Stuart.
但是我不想走
But I want to stay.
Stuart 别磨叽!
Stuart, now!
我知道他挺二逼的
You know, I know he's a jerk,
但是我有点为他难过
but I actually feel bad for him.
你看到问题所在了吧
And now you see the problem.
快上来 你这熊孩子!
Come on, you pain in the ass!
说我呢!
That's me!
拜 Stuart
Bye, Stuart.
等等!
Wait!
我也是熊孩子啊!
I'm a pain in the ass, too!
和Raj能和好
Are you relieved that you and Raj
是不是让你舒了口气?
were able to patch things up?
现在吗?
At the moment?
不 并没有
No, not really.
# 燃烧吧 宝贝 燃烧... #
# Burn, baby, burn... #
摇摆吧 宝贝!
Shake it, baby!
摇起来!
Work that thing!